https://www.itarus.com/privacy-statement/

Skip to content
HomePackaging
MockupsSoftware SolutionsOverviewArtworkOnlineInsightPasaraGEMTexturesPrepress  ServicesDigital Artwork & ReprographicsContract ProofsMarket samples & Ligraproofs™Virtual PhotographyDigital PrintAutomated Artwork GenerationDesign ImplementationPackaging PrototypesComputer to PlateLeverage ServicesDelivering Cost SavingsSpeed to MarketPreserving Your Brand EquityPrint Quality ManagementColour ManagementProcess EfficiencyInformation SystemsAbout UsWhy Choose Us?Whats’ the Point?How Do We Help?Our HistoryPartnerships & AccreditationGet in TouchContact UsCareersTerms of UsePrivacy StatementWho We HelpRetailersBrand OwnersPharmaceuticalsMarketingBuying / ProcurementSolution Managers– Hot News –
Search for:
Privacy StatementWPTestAdmin2018-06-14T15:22:32+00:00
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Itarus Limited is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Itarus Limited Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Itarus Limited website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Itarus Limited collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name and telephone number.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Itarus Limited. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Itarus Limited for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Itarus Limited Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Itarus Limited public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Itarus Limited does not read any of your private online communications.
Itarus Limited encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Itarus Limited so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Itarus Limited is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Itarus Limited and Itarus Limited family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Itarus Limited collects and uses your personal information to operate the Itarus Limited Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Itarus Limited also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Itarus Limited and its affiliates. Itarus Limited may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Itarus Limited does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Itarus Limited may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Itarus Limited may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Itarus Limited, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Itarus Limited keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Itarus Limited, in order to determine what Itarus Limited services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Itarus Limited to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Itarus Limited Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Itarus Limited or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Itarus Limited; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Itarus Limited, or the public.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise Itarus Limited pages, or register with Itarus Limited site or services, a cookie helps Itarus Limited to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Itarus Limited Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Itarus Limited features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Itarus Limited services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Itarus Limited secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Itarus Limited secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Itarus Limited will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Itarus Limited encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Itarus Limited is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Itarus Limited welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Itarus Limited has not adhered to this Statement, please contact:
Robert Leigh
ICT Operations & Security Manager
Itarus Limited
Itarus House
Tenter Road
Northampton
United Kingdom
NN3 6PZ
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
